(
"ai_sub_version": "2.9.1",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 7,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 15,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch"
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 5,
"max": 5,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
終わらないで
Please don't let it end...
ここに宣言します！セブンスホイッスル
Here, I declare! 7th Whistle!
ひとつ、病める時も 健やかなる時もずっと
One, through times of sickness or health, I'll always...
愛を歌い続けることを堂々と誓います
...proudly swear to keep singing of love!
ふたつ、トークだとかダンスももっと追求します
Two, I'll pursue MC-ing and dancing even more!
みっつ、ずっと推してもらえるアイドルになってみせます
Three, I'll show you I can become an idol who's always supported!
よっつ、不安な未来も私が照らすんだ
Four, I will shine upon the anxious future!
それでも落ち込んじゃう日は
Even on days when I feel down,
思い出しているよ みんなのその笑顔 その声
I'll remember everyone's smiles and voices!
ハッピーラッキーセブン革命！
Happy Lucky Seven Revolution!
サンデイ マンデイ この先ずっと一緒だよね 約束
Sunday, Monday, from here on out forever, we'll be together, that's a promise!
ほらね、笑う門には空来る
See, where there is laughter, the sky comes!
ハッピーバースデイ！毎日がほら チューズデイ ウェンズデイ ラッキーデイ
Happy Birthday! Look, every day is Tuesday, Wednesday, Lucky day!
生まれ変わっても 迷わずに
Even if I'm reborn, without hesitation,
君だけのアイドルになるよ
I will become your one and only idol!
何度も見つけてね セブンスホイッスル
Find me again and again! 7th Whistle!
いつつ、アイドルとは時にあざとさも必要？
Five, as an idol, is cuteness sometimes necessary?
誰かが言ってたけど うまくできないの、ねぇ！
Someone said that, but I can't do it very well, right?
むっつめは私から お願い聞いて？
Six, please listen to my request?
推し変なんてしないでよね！私を見て！
Don't change your fave! Look only at me!
ハッピーラッキーセブン革命！
Happy Lucky Seven Revolution!
2026.01.10
Tokyo International Forum
January 10, 2026
いっくよー！
Here we go!
楽しさに釣られ
Lured by the fun,
うっかり探したら
I searched carelessly,
知らないあれやこれ
and found all sorts of things...
めぐり逢えた
...I had never known.
大変な挑戦も
Tough challenges
のんびり休息も
and relaxing breaks,
支え合って想い
we supported each other,
伝染した
and our feelings connected.
見劣りしたって
Even if we look inferior,
前を向いて
let's look forward.
小さな歩重ねていこう
Let's take small steps forward together.
絶えず途切れない
Among the endless,
笑い声の中を進んでいこう
unceasing laughter, let's keep moving.
さあ！
Now!
教えて ほら 全部
Come on, tell me everything!
何回 時計の針 ぐるぐる 回っても
No matter how many times the clock hands spin round and round,
話を聞くよ
I will listen to you.
まだまだ 終わらない
It's far from over,
この夢がきっと ずっと
this dream will surely last forever.
永遠に 褪せることのない
Giving you a time
時をキミにくれる
that will never fade.
訪れた先で
Wherever we visit,
歓迎増えていく
the welcome grows.
すれ違った風に
Like I heard it
聞いたみたい
from the passing wind.
そして世界中も
And let's involve
巻き込んでいこうよ
the entire world too!
一人また一人
One by one,
加わった
they joined in.
ちょっと漂って
Drifting around a bit,
街を探す
we search the town.
望遠鏡 覗いてもわからない
I don't know, even looking through a telescope.
迷っているのも
Even being lost...
それが醍醐味だって
...is the best part of it,
言っていいよ
you can say.
ねえ！
Hey!
たくさんの 思い出を
So many memories,
こぼさないように ぎゅっと しまって
pack them tightly so they won't spill,
輝きを 大切に 運び続ける
and keep carrying this brilliance with care.
出会えた 瞬間に
The moment we met,
こんな場所を選んで防衛する
having chosen a place like this,
パッと 広げ
let's spread it open
見せつけていこう
and show it off!
次はキミの元へ
Next, to where you are!
はい！ はい！ はい！ はい！ はい！ はい！ はい！ はい！
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
さあ
Come on,
教えて　ほら全部
tell me, show me everything!
何回　時計の針がぐるぐる回っても
No matter how many times the clock hands turn around,
話を聞くよ
I will listen to you.
終わらない
This never-ending...
この夢がきっとずっと永遠に
...dream will surely, forever,
色褪せることのない
never fade away,
ときを君にくれる
giving you times of joy.
La la la...
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Go! Go! Go! Go!
みんな手拍子もやってね！
Everyone, please clap your hands too!
あんなに詰め込んだ
The dreams we stuffed so full
夢はくしゃくしゃで
are all crumpled up,
勇気がいるけれど
and though it takes courage,
君にだけは言えるよ
I can say it only to you.
隣だから
Because we're side by side,
一緒に行けるかな
can we go together?
おはよー！ 新しい今日にご挨拶
Good morning! Greeting a new day today too!
ってあれ？ 嘘！ もうこんな時間？
Wait, what? No way! It's already this time?!
おでかけ予定あるのに
Even though I have plans to go out,
すぐに支度をしなきゃ
I must get ready quickly!
行ってきます！
I'm off!
慌てて飛び出して気づく
I rushed out only to realize...
こっちじゃない！ こっちだっけ？
Not this way! Is it this way?
助けてーー！ 空も！
Help me, Sora too!
トラブルばっか 転んで起きての毎日です
Nothing but trouble, falling down and getting up every day.
なんでも思い通りとか そんな美味しい話はないけれど
There's no sweet deal where everything goes your way, but...
心の曇り トラブル放す合言葉 唱えて
Reciting the password to clear my mind's clouds and cast away trouble,
おはように ほら 快晴でしょう ずっと
Saying "Good morning," look, it's completely clear, forever!
みんなに届けたい 歌もダンスも元気も
I want to deliver to everyone my singing, dancing, and energy too!
いつも同じ空の下 笑顔も分け合えるよ
Under the same sky as always, we can share our smiles.
ちょっと疲れちゃう時も 涙が出そうな時も
Even when I get a little tired, or when I feel like crying,
いつも魔法の言葉で 今日も てらせ らせらの空！
With the magic words as always, today too, light up Rasera's sky!
せーの！ てらせらせら！
Ready, set... terase rasera!
みんな声出してーー！
Everyone, let me hear your voices!
今日も一日がんばろう
Let's do our best today too!
カメラにマイクに よし準備OK！
Camera, microphone, alright, preparation OK!
お水もちゃんとあるし
I have my water ready too,
そなえさえあれば嬉しいです
as long as I'm prepared, I'm happy!
それじゃ今日は何をしようかな？ お歌に雑談に あ、トラブル！
Well then, what shall I do today? Singing, chatting, ah, trouble!
みんなと笑い合わせば また明日も晴れ晴れだ よっしゃ！
If we laugh together, tomorrow will be sunny again! Alright!
みんな声出してーー！
Everyone, let me hear your voices!
ふうとため息こぼして ふと夜空を見上げたら
With a soft sigh, when I suddenly look up at the night sky,
ぽっと満天の星たちが キラキラ瞬いていた
Suddenly, the starry sky twinkles brightly.
ずっと追いかけ続けたい 雲より高い夢でも
I want to keep chasing it forever, even if it's a dream higher than the clouds.
もっと強く羽ばたいて 空まで駆け抜けていくよ
Flapping my wings even stronger, I will run all the way to the sky!
そっと背中を押すような ぬくもりに包まれたから
Because I was wrapped in a warmth that gently pushes my back,
いつまでもそばにいたい 今日も明日も ずっと
I want to be by your side forever, today, tomorrow, and always.
てらせ らせらの空！ せーの！
Light up Rasera's sky! Ready, set...
てらせらせら！
...terase rasera!
みんなーー！
Everyone!
新年、明けまして...
Happy...
...おめでとうございますーー！
...New Year!
本日は、お寒いなか、ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much for coming in this cold weather today!
みんな来れた？
Could everyone make it?
あ、来れてるからいるの分かってる、あの、ちゃんと、安全に来れましたか？
Ah, I know you made it since you're here. Um, did you all arrive safely?
え、今回のソロライブは、えっと、私のライブ史上最大規模ということで、凄く大きな会場で
So, this solo live is, um, the largest scale in my live show history, in an incredibly big venue.
あの、ハッシュタグとかも見てたんだけど、「でかっ！」って。「でかいの凄いな」って書いてる人がいっぱいいて
And, I was looking at the hashtags and saw things like, "It's huge!" and "The size is amazing!"
私も「でかいな、凄いな」って思いながら見てました。
I was also looking at it thinking, "It really is huge, how amazing!"
リハーサルの時は、「ここ、ここにいっぱいそらともさん来るね」って言われて
During rehearsals, they told me, "A lot of Soratomo-san are going to fill this place up!"
「え、誰もいないじゃん！誰もいないよ！誰もいない...」
"But wait, there's no one here! Nobody's here! Nobody..."
っていう会話をしながら、え、とても楽しくやっておりました。
While having that conversation, we had a lot of fun.
でもみんないるね、ありがとう！
But everyone is actually here! Thank you!
というわけで、今日！初めて！ライブだよって人ー！
So, is there anyone here for whom today is their very first live concert?
おー、結構いるねー
Oh, quite a few!
じゃあ、現地自体初めてだよって人！
Then, how about people for whom it's their first time being at the actual venue?
結構いる、ありがとう！
Quite a few! Thank you!
じゃあ、がんばって、あ、手振るだけでいいからね、あの
Now then, do your best—ah, just waving is fine, okay? Um...
女の子ーー！
Girls!
おー！声出してくれてありがとう！「キャー！」聞こえた！
Oh! Thank you for raising your voices! I heard a "Kyah!"
男の子ーー！
Boys!
おー！ありがとうございます！
Oh! Thank you very much!
え、これってあれ、ペンライトとかできんのかな？あ、できないのかな？え、でき、できるかな？
Um, can we do the penlight thing? Ah, can we not? Can we do it?
こちらのひと、赤ー！
People on this side, red!
こちらの人は、青ー！
People on this side, blue!
真ん中のは、黄色ー！
And the middle, yellow!
わぁ、すごーい！きれいだぁ！
Wow, amazing! It's so beautiful!
こんな感じでですね、今日はペンライトでも遊べちゃうということで
Just like this, we can play with penlights today...
ぜひぜひみんなでも楽しんでいきましょう！
so let's definitely have fun together, everyone!
いえーい！
Yay!
今日はみんなも主役だよ！
Everyone is the main star today!
いえーい！
Yay!
まだ飲んでない！
I haven't drunk it yet!
お耳可愛い？ありがとう！
My ears are cute? Thank you!
もうちょっと飲もう。
I'll drink a bit more.
ねぇ、ねぇ！
Hey, hey!
お水だって分かったじゃん。後ろ見たいから？
You already knew it was water. Is it because you want to see my back?
ありがとう！
Thank you!
さあ、というわけでね、今日はいかがだったでしょうか...とはいかないので
So then, how did you like today's... wait, we can't end it like that!
始まったばかり！
It's only just begun!
なんですが！なんと、もう言っていいのかな？
But guess what! Is it okay to say it now?
YouTubeの配信は...
The YouTube stream...
なんと、ここまでなんです！
is actually ending here!
お怒りー！
Don't be mad!
でも、続き見たい人は...
But for those who want to see the rest...
どこだ？ここ？ここ？
Where is it? Here? Or here?
ここら辺に、あの、チケットとか買えると...
Around here... around here you can buy tickets...
買えるって言い方やだ、見に来てね！
I hate saying "buy", please just come watch us!
チカチカしとる、すごい！
It's flashing, amazing!
というわけで、先にどんどん行ってみましょうか！
So then, let's keep moving forward!
盛り上がっていきましょう！
Let's get hyped!
楽しんでいこう！
Let's have fun!
それじゃあ、盛り上がっていこうよ！
Alright, let's get hyped!
ドキドキ ドキドキ 響いてるよ
My heart is pounding, pounding, and echoing...
冒頭無料配信はこちらで終了です。
[The free preview broadcast ends here.]